基于真实故事改编
伦敦
下议院餐厅
你听到智者哈罗德怎么评价对罗德西亚[现津巴布韦]的访问了吗
Hear what Harold the Wise said about the trip to Rhodesia?
下议院餐厅
"我对此非常 非常 非常失望"
"I would be very, very, very disappointed."
"我对此非常 非常 非常失望 我的狗也是"
"I would be very, very, very disappointed, and so would my whippet."
-鞑靼牛肉 先生  -非常感谢
- Steak tartare, sir. - Thank you very much indeed.
巴塞尔先生
So, Senor Besselli,
我得到消息 约翰·帕多基本证实了
I have news. John Pardoe has practically confirmed it.
格里蒙德再过一年就退休 最多18个月
Grimond is stepping down. One more year, 18 months at the most.
如果是假的 我会"非常 非常 非常失望"
I would be "very, very, very disappointed" if that's not true.
那就恭喜你了 你想想
What can I say but, congratulations? Just think, though,
考虑到权力制衡
given the balance of power,
下一任自由党党魁有可能当上副首相
the next leader of the Liberal Party could be Deputy Prime Minister.
没错
Well, quite.
我不介意去掉这个副字
I never did care very much for the word deputy.
我会支持你的 一直都会
Well, I'll be there for you, all the way.
当然了 资金永远都是问题
Finance is going to be a problem, of course, as ever.
我很想帮你 可我又不是百万富翁
Well, I'd love to help, but I'm not exactly a millionaire.
我只能待在一个屋顶漏水的办公室里
And I'm stuck here in an office with a leaky roof
自己的员工都快请不起了
and I can't even afford my own staff.
话说你最喜欢哪个秘书 伊丽莎白吗
Tell me, what's that secretary of yours like, Elizabeth?
-怎么样  -床上工夫了得
- Any good? - Oh, yes. Particularly in bed.
佩德罗
Pedro!
我爱死你了
I adore you!
你胃口还真不小
You and your monstrous appetites!
你不是传道的吗
Weren't you a lay preacher?
至少你以前是
Well, obviously you were, literally.
算是爱好吧 就像有人喜欢高尔夫
Call it a hobby. Some people play golf,
我喜欢播种
I like screwing.
私下跟你说 我还年轻的时候
Between the two of us, when I was young,
饥不择食起来 我会去找雄性的慰藉
I was so desperate, I'd go looking on the spear side.
你是说... 你... 喜欢同性
Are you telling me... that you... were usable?
是的 多少有一点吧
I'm a little bit so, yes.
没吓到你吧
If that's not too shocking.
彼得·佩德罗·巴塞尔·冯·巴塞巴赫
Peter Pedro Bessell von Bessellbach!
在这间屋子里 我大概是最不会被吓到的
Well, out of anyone in this room, I'm probably the least shocked of all,
你明白我意思吗
if you understand my meaning.
-我明白  -这年头这事已经不稀奇了吧
- I think so. - It's hardly a great surprise now, is it?
应该... 不稀奇
I... suppose not.
男女你更倾向哪一边
What would you say you are, vis-a-vis men and women?
什么比例 五五开吗
What are you? 50-50?
应该是二八开吧
More like 80-20.
八成喜欢女人
I mean, 80% for the ladies.
嗯
Yeah.
我也是二八开 只不过... 八成是... 男同
Yes, I call myself 80%, but... 80%...gay.
天啊 这个词在这种地方没人说过吧
Gosh, I'm not sure that word's ever been said within these walls before.
至少不是这么用的 我太太坚持认为这个词指"开心"
Not in that context. My wife insists that gay means happy.
她说得完全没错
I think she's absolutely right.
我确实很开心 一直都很开心
And I intend to be very happy, very many times in my life.
尤其是跟他在一起的时候
And very much so with him.
非常 非常 非常开心
Very, very, very much so.
小心点 祸从口出
Careful, now. Keep it discreet.
还没有谁值得你为他进监狱
I'm not sure any boy's worth ending up in prison for.
-你在保护我吗 佩德罗  -需要的话 杰里米
- You protecting me, Pedro? - If I must, Jeremy,
-我会保护你的  -终于啊
- then I will. - At last!
谢天谢地 终于有人保护我不被自己害死了
Thank God, someone to protect me from myself.
我得点杯葡萄酒 庆祝一下
I am going to order some port, to celebrate.
彼得 我们就是这世上的两个老女王
Peter, we are nothing but a pair of old queens.
敬... 女王陛下
To... Her Majesty.
敬女王陛下
Her Majesty.
英式丑闻
马森宫廷酒店
-早 乔缇  -早 杰里米
- Morning, Jonty. - Morning, Jeremy.
早上好 先生
Morning, sir.
我有责任告知首相先生
It is my duty to inform the Prime Minister
要是他继续限制移民入境
that if he continues to restrict immigration,
将会堵塞国家的新鲜血液...
he is staunching the lifeblood of this country...
是啊 同意
Hear, hear!
... 更何况
... and, and fuelling the rise of
还会为"不列颠只有白人"运动  煽风点火
the "Keep Britain White" campaign.
英联邦所属国的所有公民
Citizens from all over the Commonwealth
均有权安全自由地来到英国 否则
deserve a free and safe right of entry, or else
政府就会发觉它签署的白皮书就是一纸空文
the Government may find that its White Paper is very aptly named.
-我是巴塞尔  -佩德罗 出事了
- Bessell speaking. - Pedro, I have a problem.
中午12点 丽兹酒店见面说
Meet me at The Ritz, 12 o'clock.
这玩意上周寄到我妈那儿 她看过了
It was delivered last week to my mother, and she read it,
整整17页 一字不落
every single word, all 17 pages.
"诺曼·约瑟夫 寄"
"From Norman Josiffe?"
你是说 他是你的...
You mean, he's one of your...
"杰里米和我是同性伴侣关系..."
"Jeremy and I have had a homosexual relationship..."
我的天 你母亲看过了
Oh, my God, your mother read this?!
他想要什么 钱吗
What does he want? Money?
一共只要30英镑
The vast sum of £30.
连敲诈都不会
He can't even blackmail properly.
他到底是谁
Well, who is he, exactly?
他是...
He is, um...
... 我们初识的时候 他...
... well, when I first met him, he was...
... 宛如天使
... very heaven.
四年前
早上好
Good morning.
今天天气可真不错
And a very, very fine morning it is, too.
早上好 先生 抱歉
Good morning, sir. Pardon me.
我叫杰里米·索普 来过周末的
Jeremy Thorpe. I've come to stay for the weekend.
范·德·维特先生请我来的
I'm a guest of Mr. Van de Vater.
我知道 他提过 可兴奋了
I know, sir. He said. He was very excited.
您是一位特殊的客人
Quite a special visitor.
议会高官呢
Member of Parliament and all of that.
-你叫什么  -我叫诺曼 先生
- What's your name? - Norman, sir.
你也叫诺曼
Another Norman?
屋主叫诺曼·范·德·法特 你叫诺曼...
Mein host, Norman Van de Vater and Norman...
约瑟夫  -约瑟夫
- Josiffe. - Josiffe!
-是法语吗  -我也不知道 先生
- What is that, French? - Um, I don't know, sir.
真的吗
Really?
你没有挖掘过家姓的来源吗
You've never so much as enquired about your own surname?
只是因为我母亲嫁给了一个姓约瑟夫的
It's just, um, my mother married a Josiffe,
但他不是我生父
but he's not my father.
-还真是挺复杂的  -对不起
- Ah, complicated, yes. - Sorry.
没有的事 都怪我 这是隐私
No, no, no, no. My fault, my fault. It's private.
我得接着干活了
Well, I'd best get back to work.
您周末骑马吗
Will you be riding this weekend, sir?
当然了
Oh, yeah, yeah, definitely.
这是我的... 一大兴趣
It's a great... great passion of mine.
我可以帮您备马
I can prepare the horse myself.
您是什么水平
What level are you at?
习惯怎样的马鞍
What kind of mount would suit you best?
只要... 适合我的就行了
Well, just... the right sort of mount for me, really.
说不好
It depends.
你呢 诺曼 我猜你一定是个马术大师
What about you, Norman? You're the great expert, I see.
能跟马在一起
It's all I've ever wanted to do, sir.
是我从小梦寐以求的工作
Working with horses. Ever since I was a kid.
我的家人... 我们有些矛盾
My family wasn't... We had our problems.
糟心的家事 都是我自己的错
All sorts of nonsense. It was my own fault, really, but
但我总会自己去马厩 然后...
I could always find my way to the stables and,
... 自得其乐
... be happy.
我太话痨了 大家都这么说
I talk too much. Everyone says.
哪有 多有意思 你跑哪儿去了
No, no, no. It's marvellous. Where are you?
别被任何人牵着鼻子走
Don't let anyone ever tell you to stop.
您真好 先生 非常感谢
You're very kind, sir, thank you.
叫我杰里米 该叫我什么
Jeremy. What's my name?
杰里米
Jeremy.
我在想 只是随便想想
I wonder, it's just a thought, but if you ever
诺曼 要是你离开了屋主诺曼
move on from Norman, Norman,
来到了伦敦
and you find yourself in London,
不如来找我吧 意下如何
why don't you get in touch? Would that be all right?
再好不过了 先生 杰里米
Yes, sir. Jeremy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好 那我就先... 溜了
Right. Well, I must... trot on.
然后 时隔一年多...
And, lo and behold, just over a year later...
-请进  -打扰一下 索普先生
- Yeah! - Excuse me, Mr. Thorpe.
大厅有一位访客 他说跟您有约
A visitor for you, Central Lobby. Says you're expecting him.
诺曼·约瑟夫先生
A Mr. Norman Josiffe.
对 对 没错
Yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
这就过去
Right away.
-格雷汉姆  -杰里米
- Graham. - Jeremy.
诺曼
Norman!
真抱歉 我实在没地方可去了
I'm so sorry. I couldn't think where else to go.
-希望您不介意  -当然不会
- I hope you don't mind. - No, no.
不好意思 当心蒂什夫人
Oh, sorry. Mind Mrs. Tish.
我会的 你好 蒂什夫人
I certainly will. Hello, Mrs. Tish.
我真是忙疯了
Well, I am grotesquely busy,
不过应该还有时间聊会儿天
but we might have time for a quick confab.
他说我们不能进去
Oh, he said we're not allowed in.
非常抱歉 索普先生 您知道规矩的
I'm sorry, Mr. Thorpe, but you know the rules.
威斯敏斯特宫禁止犬只入内
No dogs allowed inside the Palace of Westminster.
是没错 不过 你也知道
Now, that is true, except, as you well know,
查尔斯二世签署了法令
Charles II issued an edict
允许查理斯王小猎犬入宫
allowing King Charles Spaniels inside the domain,
虽然严格来说 这是条杰克罗素犬
and while this might be technically a Jack Russell,
-没错吧  -对
- is that right? - That's right.
你也知道狗的德行 我看流浪的猎犬
You know what dogs are like, and I think that some roving
可能就跟蒂什夫人的妈妈有一腿
spaniel might have had his way with Mrs. Tish's mother.
这就意味着她也有王室血统
Which means that she has royal blood,
所以请为我们让路吧 来
so I must ask you, make way, please. Come.
谢谢
Thank you.
查尔斯二世的事纯属瞎编
Complete fantasy, that Charles II thing.
并没有这条法令
There is no such law.
不过这么多年来人人都在传
But so many people have said it over the years,
就当它是真的吧
it's assumed to be true,
记着这个还是挺有用的
which is a very good thing to remember in life, I think.
我必须离开那儿 就想到您了
I just had to get away, and I thought of you.
范·德·法特先生对我说了非常伤人的话
Mr. Van de Vater said the most terrible things to me, really,
我从没听过哪位绅士这么说话
I've never heard a gentleman talk like that.
只跟你说
Well, strictly between ourselves,
他根本就算不上什么绅士
he's not really a gentleman at all.
他的一生全在做戏
It's a charade, his entire life.
他真名叫诺曼·法特 是威尔士人
His real name is Norman Vater, from Wales.
他非常崇拜你 简直了 天哪
Well, he adored you. Absolutely. Oh, my God.
"杰里米这个 杰里米那个"
"Jeremy this, Jeremy that."
每次收到你的信 他都会大声读出来
Every time you wrote to him, he'd read it out loud.
比如什么
Like what?
具体一点的
Anything in particular?
您在玛格丽特公主
You sent a postcard on the day
和安东尼·阿姆斯特朗-琼斯订婚的时候
Princess Margaret got engaged to Anthony Armstrong-Jones,
寄过一张明信片 上面写着
and you wrote to Mr. Van de Vater,
"真是幸福的一对" 杰里米写道
"Of the happy couple," Jeremy says,
"太可惜了 我倒是想娶一个 骗一个"
"what a pity. I'd rather hoped to marry one and seduce the other."
不过他对这些明信片的所作所为更恶劣
But it wasn't so much that as what he did with the postcards.
我要妥善保管 珍藏起来
I'll keep this safe and sound, add it to my little collection.
都是有权有势的人写给我的信
Letters from the great and powerful.
他放进了一个抽屉
He put them in a drawer.
我不知道他都留下来了
I didn't know he kept them, no.
不过再也不会了
Well, he doesn't any more.
我走的时候把它们都带出来了
I took them, when I walked out.
走 蒂什夫人
Come, Mrs Tish.
你真是太贴心了
But that is exceedingly kind of you.
你为什么会这么做呢
Whatever would you do that for?
有些信件很私人 还有点...
Some of those are personal and a bit...
... 放荡 恕我冒昧
... cheeky, if you don't mind my saying.
而且 如果落在坏人手里...
And, um, if they fell into the wrong hands...
... 我不想你惹上麻烦
... I wouldn't want you getting into trouble.
谢谢你
Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
很搞笑吧 他叫诺曼 我也叫诺曼
It's funny, his name's Norman and my name's Norman
而这些都写给"亲爱的诺曼"
and those are all, "Dear Norman",
我曾经想象过...
and I used to imagine...
... 是写给我的
...they were mine.
好像你这样的人会给我写信一样
As if a man like you would ever write to a man like me.
也不是不可能
Well, it's not impossible.
真的吗
Really?
-我能喝点水吗  -当然
- Can I have some water? - Yes, of course, yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
这些药是新开的 我以前吃氯普马嗪
These pills are new. I was on Largactil,
后来他们让我试试阿米替林
but they said to try Elavil instead.
因为我脑子不太好使
Because I wasn't very well in the head.
你肯定已经猜到了
I'm sure you guessed that already.
我住过院... 是精神病人
I was in a clinic... for psychiatric patients.
-你介意吗  -当然不会
- Is that all right?  - Mm, yeah, of course.
他们人很好 真的
And they were very good, they really were,
我很感激
and I'm very grateful,
可他们现在说
but then they said,
"我们帮不了你了"
"There's not much more we can do for you,"
我说 "那我现在该怎么办"
so I said, "Well, what do I do now?"
他们说 "我们管不了"
and they said, "That's not up to us,"
我又说 "那好吧..."
and I said, "Well..."
我想到了你
And that's when I thought of you.
你有什么期待
And with a view to what, exactly?
是这样 我从范·德·法特先生家逃跑的时候
Well, the thing is, when I ran away from Mr Van de Vater,
忘了拿社保卡
I had to leave my National Insurance card behind,
而现在很难拿回来 至少现在不行
and I can hardly ask for it back, can I? Not now,
也就是说我没法工作
which means I won't be able to work,
没工作 就没地方住
and if I can't get work then I can't get a place to live,
如果没有固定地址
and if I don't have a permanent address,
就拿不到处方药
then I can't get my prescription,
我走投无路了 杰里米 而且...
so I'm stuck, Jeremy, I'm completely stuck, and...
... 我连住的地方都没有
... I've got nowhere to stay.
你把他带到你母亲家里了
You took him to your mother's house?
为什么啊
But why?
我觉得会很有意思
I thought it would be fun.
-这是谁  -厄休拉 这位是彼得·弗里曼
- Who might this be?  - Ursula, this is Peter Freeman.
他是摄影师
He is a cameraman.
要和我一起去马耳他考察
He's coming with me on that expedition to Malta.
我说可以留他过夜的 对吧
I said we could give him a bed for the night, hmm?
五 六 七 八
Five, six, seven, eight.
加快
Faster.
他们说 你也是贵族委员会的一员
They say you're part of it, this committee regarding peerages.
不 我没加入 不存在的
Oh, no, I'm not on the committee, no, no.
可它因你而存在 是你一手促成的
But it exists because of you. You facilitated it.
我只是在对的时间问了对的问题而已
I just asked the right question at the right time, that's all.
站在谁的立场
For whose benefit?
安东尼·韦奇伍德·本恩吗
Anthony Wedgwood Benn?
他是我牛津的校友 是个相当不错的小伙
I knew him at Oxford. He is a perfectly decent chap.
他是个托洛茨基分子
The man's a Trot.
-要顾全大局  -谢谢 珍妮
- Think of the bigger picture.  - Thank you very much, Jenny.
如果你插手这个委员会 操控得当
If you sit on that committee and steer it correctly,
有朝一日就能被封为索普男爵
then one day you could claim the ancient Barony of Thorpe.
-不是很棒吗  -应该是吧
- Wouldn't that be marvellous?  - I suppose it would, yes.
你会被提拔的 亲爱的
You would be elevated, darling.
提拔
Elevated.
乖 蒂什夫人 躺下
There you go, Mrs Tish. Lie down.
好孩子
Good girl.
晚安 蒂什夫人
Night-night, Mrs Tish.
没出什么问题吧
There's nothing wrong, is there?
怎么会出问题呢
Why would there be?
我不知道
I don't know.
那本书看了吗
Did you read the book?
-还没有  -我觉得你会喜欢的
- Well, not yet.  - I think you'll like it.
别这么害怕
Don't look so scared.
-我没有  -你有
- I'm not.  - Yes, you are.
你像只吓坏了的小兔子
You're like a frightened little rabbit.
是你吗
Is that what you are?
你是... 我的小兔子吗
Are you... my little bunny?
怎么了
Oh, what's this?
亲爱的 怎么了这是
Well, dear, dear. What's all this?
到底怎么了
What's all this?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你在这儿很开心 不是吗
You've had a nice time, haven't you?
那怎么哭了呢
Then why so sad?
从来没人对我这么好过
No-one's ever been this kind to me.
"从来没人对我这么好过"
"No-one's ever been this kind to me."
可怜的小兔子
Poor little bunny rabbit.
别傻了 好了
Don't be silly. Come on.
把眼泪擦了
Wipe your eyes.
就是这样 擦干净
That's it, that's it. Dry your face.
我看看 难过都甩掉
Let me see. And shake it off.
再来
And again.
好多了
Much better.
现在我要吻你了 你会很享受的
Now I'm going to kiss you, and you will enjoy it.
-其实你可以更享受的  -我不能
- Well, you could enjoy it a bit more. - I can't.
为什么
Why not?
这样不对
It's wrong.
没有什么不对
Well, That's not wrong.
现在 铺上这个 以防万一
Now, we are going to need this, just in case.
还有每个单身汉都需要的一点帮助
And a good little helping of every bachelor's friend.
手脚撑起来 乖
Just hop onto all fours, there's a good chap.
这样最舒服了不是吗
That always works best, don't you think?
-在床上吗  -对 在床上
- On the bed?  - Yes, on the bed.
这就对了
There we are.
很好
That's it.
记住... 隔壁是我母亲的房间
And remember... mother's room.
然后呢
And then?
-吃干抹净  -懂了
- We did the deed. - Of course.
天哪
Gosh.
这个非常 非常好吃
It's very, very good, this.
-真好吃 很难得放了很多柠檬  -是啊
- It's excellent. Quite a lot of lemon, which is rare. - Yeah.
你再次有诺曼的消息是...
So the next time you heard from Norman was...
-... 这次吗  -不 不是
- ... was this? - No, no, no, no, no.
我把他直接从母亲家里接出来了
I took him straight from mother's and moved him into rooms.
租了房子 金屋藏娇
Paid the rent, kept him there.
小兔子
Bunny?
进行曲开始了 这是我们的故事 关于你和我
The march begins, and this is our story. This is you and me.
这是... 是人类在向造物者行进
This is... this is mankind marching towards his maker.
感觉到了吗
Feel it?
也许这就是布鲁克纳所寻找的
Maybe that's what Bruckner's searching for
神和天堂
God and his heaven,
妙不可言
and it's ineffable.
我在那儿住过几个月 哈灵顿路上
I used to live there for a couple of months, Harrington Road.
-房子很漂亮  -那边可不是
- Rather nice houses. - Not down that end.
五人挤一间 我们还得去公园尿尿
Five to a room. We had to go and piss in the park.
这是你第一次坐巴士吗
Is this your first time on a bus?
才不是
No, it's not.
-肯定是  -不好意思 我坐过的巴士多了
- I bet it is.  - Excuse me, I have been on a great many buses.
-骗人  -我当时16岁
- Liar!  - Well, when I was 16,
有个小假期 可以离校一天
we used to have short leave, like a day out from school.
我们会去帕丁顿
We'd come up to Paddington,
坐36路巴士到伦敦大板球场 偷偷带几瓶啤酒
get the number 36 bus to Lord's, smuggle on bottles of beer.
-可淘气了  -我们是指你和自大狂勋爵吗
- It was very wicked.  - We being you and Lord Snooty?
是啊 自大狂老哥
Yes, that's right. Good old Snooty.
-他怎么样  -好的不能再好了
- How is Snooty?  - He's absolutely top-hole, ripping.
从发展和投资来看
This country's application to join the Common Market
我国申请加入欧共体
represents a huge opportunity,
都是巨大的机遇
for growth and investment,
不光是对伦敦的银行家和企业家
and not just for the bankers and businessmen in London
他们已经赚得盆满钵满了
they have lined their pockets enough -
更为了我们北德文郡的选民
but for my constituents in North Devon,
为了这片土地上所有勤恳工作的人民
and for all the good and honest workers across the land,
欧洲代表了大胆全新的视野
Europe represents a bold new horizon -
我们可以从中获利并学习
an undertaking from which we may profit and learn,
从而造福子孙后代
and enrich our lives for generations to come.
"我不想说轻浮的话
"I wasn't going to say anything compromising,
可还是忍不住
but can't stop myself saying,
'我爱你 迫不及待想见你'
'I love you and can't wait to see you'.
爱你的 杰里米"
"Yours affectionately, Jeremy."
小兔子
Buuuuuu-nny!
我整天一个人呆着
I'm left on my own all day.
别这么幼稚 你知道我多忙吗
Oh, for God's sake. Do you realise how busy I am?
可我还能做什么呢
But what am I supposed to do?!
我希望你答应我 只要回到伦敦
Well, I want you to promise, if you're ever back in London,
一定要联系我 好吗
to get in touch. Yes?
干杯
Cheers.
也许是时候考虑下一步了...
Maybe it's time you thought about moving on...
... 做点实事
... doing something with your life.
你觉得呢 小兔子
What do you think, Bunny?
那所马术学校 后来怎么说
That dressage school, whatever happened to that?
学校很好 但我去不了
That would be wonderful, but I can't.
在法国
It's in France.
"... 很快 小兔子就能去巴黎了
"... In haste, Bunnies can and will go to France.
"爱你的 杰里米"
"Yours affectionately, Jeremy."
巴黎又他妈怎么了
But what happened to bloody France?!
他们拒绝了我 可这又不能怪我
They said no. Go on, how is that my fault?!
我在马场给你找了别的工作 你又不肯去
Well, I got you that other job at the stables and you threw that away.
我说了 是那个男的太卑鄙
I told you! It was that man, he was vile to me!
你要是你少喝酒 少吃那些药...
Dare I say that if you drank a little less and took fewer of those pills...
怎么 你觉得我为什么需要吃药
Why is that? Why do you think I need them?
因为你 你对我做的那些事
Because of you, the things you've done to me.
是吗 你这话什么意思
Oh, really, what is that supposed to mean?
杰里米 你把同性恋的病毒传染给了我
You have infected me, Jeremy, with the virus of homosexuality!
"你把同性恋的病毒传染给了我"
"You've infected me with the virus of homosexuality."
他去哪儿了
Where did he go?
天知道
God knows.
我来揭发我跟杰里米·索普议员的
I've come to tell you about my homosexual relations
同性恋关系
with Jeremy Thorpe MP.
我是他变态欲望的受害者
I was a victim of his lust and appetites.
如果问我为什么这么久才来报警
And if you ask me why it's taken me so long to come to the police,
我只能说我被那个男人奴役了
then all I can say is that I was in thrall to the man.
这就是我的解释 被奴役
That's my explanation. In thrall.
这些可以当作证据
You have these as proof.
我给你们两个最明显的
I'll give you two of the best.
看 他的笔记 还有"小兔子"
Look. His handwriting, and "Bunnies".
我的昵称就是小兔子 证据够充分了吧
My nickname's Bunny. That's proof enough, isn't it?
剩下的我留着 谢谢
I'll keep the rest, thank you.
保险起见
It's my insurance policy.
案   件   号
杰里米·索普
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
C·费尔法克斯
苏格兰场
原始案件号
政治部
军情五处
天知道他做了什么
God knows what he got up to.
我原以为摆脱了他
I thought I was rid of him,
可谁能想到 那封信
and then, out of the blue, that,
寄给了我母亲 说出了一切
to Mother, telling her everything.
她相信了吗
Did she believe it?
没 当然没有
No, no, of course not.
他说现在住在都柏林
And now he says he's taken rooms in Dublin
得到了一位思维特曼神父的照顾
under the care of a Father Sweetman.
接下来就要靠你了
This is where you come in.
老天 要我做什么
Oh, God, doing what, exactly?
带着那封信去都柏林跟他对质
You take that thing and you confront him in Dublin.
我不能再留下笔迹 所以我要你亲自见他
I can't put anything in writing, so I need you to see him in person
警告他离开 我是认真的
and warn him off, and I mean seriously,
去把那个基佬怼翻
go and put the shits up the little sod.
告诉他这笔数额已经构成勒索
You tell him that that amounts to blackmail
要是他再这么做就会受到
and that he will have the full weight of the law upon his head
严厉制裁
if he ever tries anything like that again.
你明确告诉他 不许再联系我
And you make it very clear that he is not to contact me ever,
不许再以任何形式提起我们之前的关系
he is not to talk about our former association in any shape or form,
也不许写信给我母亲 说肛交的事
and he is not to write to my mother, describing acts of anal sex,
任何情况下都不行
under any circumstances whatsoever.
爱尔兰
都柏林
他叫诺曼·约瑟夫
His name is Norman Josiffe.
我约了他八点在这儿见面
I've asked him to meet me here at eight o'clock,
只要他一出现 必须马上告诉我
so it's imperative you let me know as soon as he turns up.
-好的 先生  -十号房 谢谢
- Certainly, sir. - Room ten, thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
老天
Oh, God!
我昨天打过电话来找诺曼 诺曼·约瑟夫
I called yesterday for Norman, Norman Josiffe.
他在吗
Is he there?
诺曼·约瑟夫先生
Mr Norman Josiffe.
诺曼
Norman?
巴塞尔先生 是吧
Mr Bessell, I take it?
我昨晚一直在等你
I was expecting you last night.
真够麻烦的 我已经等了很久了
This is highly inconvenient. I waited a very long time.
巴塞尔先生
I think you'll find, Mr Bessell,
你要知道我没义务随叫随到
that I am not at your beck and call.
尽管你是议员
You might be a Member of Parliament,
但在爱尔兰并没有权力
but that gives you no authority in Ireland,
更加管不着我
and certainly none over me.
所以 你想怎么样
Now, what do you want?
现在的问题是 我要回家了
Well, the problem is, I have to go home.
我只在这儿呆一晚 你得跟我一起
I'm only here for the one night, so you'll have to come with me
去机场 我们在路上谈
to the airport and have a word en route.
上车 麻利点
In the car. Chop chop.
我的朋友 也是同事 JT
My friend and colleague, JT,
要求你断绝和他的联系或者...
insists that you cease and desist from contacting him or...
告诉杰里米·索普我不在乎
Tell Jeremy Thorpe I don't care.
JT觉得你该收手了
JT insists that you stop.
杰里米·索普想说什么随便他
Jeremy Thorpe can say whatever he wants.
JT JT JT要求你停手
JT, JT! JT demands that you stop
否则他就会针对你采取法律措施
or he will take legal action against you.
我包里有内政部长的引渡令
I have here in this case an extradition order from the Home Secretary.
如果你还不停手
If you don't stop,
引渡令就会生效
the order will be released
把你带回英国接受审判
and you will be taken back to the United Kingdom to face trial.
-给我看看  -什么
- Show me. - What?
引渡令 给我看
The extradition order. Show me.
-就在这里 -那就给我看啊
- But it's in here.  - Show me.
你写信给他母亲了 诺曼
You wrote to his mother, Norman!
你能理解他为什么这么生气吧
You can understand why he so cross, can't you?
-他的亲生母亲  -可能是有点过分
- His own mother! - I suppose it was a bit much.
他是爱我的 他在给我的信里说过
He loved me. He wrote me a letter, it said,
"我想和你一起住在农场里"
"I want to live on a farm with you."
我不确定 难道那不是爱吗
I don't know, isn't that love?
把他遗忘在过去 不是更好吗
Wouldn't everything be better if you just left him in the past,
大家对旧情人都是这样
like everyone does with every old lover?
向前看 再找别人吧
Move on, find someone else.
-这样不好吗  -你说他是我的情人
- Wouldn't that be nice? - You called him my lover.
-是的  -谢谢你
- Yes. - Thank you.
听着 我能帮你
Look, I can help.
在你安顿好之前
I can give you £5 as a weekly retainer
我会每周给你5英磅
until you're settled.
谢谢
Thanks.
我会给你我的电话
And you can have my telephone number,
要是有什么事 联系我 不是他
so that if anything arises, you contact me, not him.
-你听明白了吗  -明白了
- You've got that? Is that clear?  - I suppose so.
-很好  -你会帮我办好社保卡吗
- Good. - And you'll sort out my National Insurance card?
-什么  -他没跟你提过 是吧
- In what way?  - Oh, he didn't tell you about that, did he?
好吧 当然不会提
Of course he didn't.
JT先生的谎话连篇
Mr JT and his fiddle-dee-dee.
他有没有说过我的生活一团糟 就因为没有这张卡
Did he tell you my life is hell because I haven't got a card?
他答应给我一张新的 可他做到了吗
He promised to get me a new one, and did he?
没有
No, he didn't!
你自己不能申请一张吗
Can't you get a new card yourself?
问题就在这儿
That's the whole point.
按道理 他是我老板
Technically, he was my employer,
因为是他付我钱 所以只能他做
because he paid for everything, so he's got to do it.
没有社保卡 我就没法工作
If I don't have a National Insurance card, I can't work,
拿不到福利 等于不存在 我就是个黑户
I don't get benefits, I don't exist. I'm like an exile here.
我知道我能做什么了
Well, I'll see what I can do.
不是你 只能是杰里米·索普
No, not you, it has to be Jeremy Thorpe!
-好吧  -那张卡是我的身份证明
- All right. - That card is my entire identity.
你会拿到卡的
You'll get your card.
-没有它我就不存在  -好了 好了 好了
- Without it, I don't exist! All right, all right, all right!
说好了... 新社保卡 5英镑
So... a new card, five quid,
我们就不再提起这些事了 好吗
and we're agreed never to discuss these things again, yes?
-是的  -就这样吗
- Yes. - Is that it?
-是的 -没有漏掉的吧
- Yes. - We've covered everything?
-是的 -谢谢
- Yes.  - Thank you.
都柏林机场
不过... 关于农场的那封信 我一直留着
Although... that letter about the farm, I kept that.
和... JT的25封情书一起保存着
I saved it, along with 25 love letters from... JT.
都好好地存放在手提箱里
And I had them all nice and safe in a suitcase,
但是我弄丢了...
which I then lost...
丢在了瑞士的...
on a train...
... 一列火车上
... in Switzerland.
-他干了什么 -他去伯尔尼找工作睡着了
- He did what?! - He went for a job in Berne and fell asleep,
-然后下了火车...  -好 但是是什么信
- and then he got off the train... - Yes, but what letters?
哪些信 他指的是哪些
Which ones? What letters did he mean?
听他描述 是情书
Well, he described them as love letters,
写在下议院信纸上
written on House of Commons notepaper,
他说蒂什夫人去世的时候 你写了很贴心的纸条
and he said you sent him a very lovely note when Mrs Tish died.
什么 那条狗 老天
Hmm? Oh, the dog. Christ!
蠢得一塌糊涂
Bloody idiot.
我们得把那些信找回来
Well, we've got to get those letters back.
早上好 我是杰里米·索普
Good morning, this is Jeremy Thorpe.
请把伯尔尼英国领事馆的电话给我
Yes, I need a number for the British Consulate in Berne, if I may.
我在找一个手提箱
Je cherche une valise.
请接外交部
Merci. Foreign Office, please.
你好
Allo?
遗失物品
Lost property. property...
物品... 有物品遗失
Property perdu, s'il vous plait. Property perdu.
找到了吗
Any luck?
-没有  -我和你说过
- Nothing. - I told you I've got that American trip
接下来两周我要去美国
for the next fortnight,
不过你还记得戴安娜·斯坦顿吗
but do you remember Diana Stainton?
-记得  -她现在在我手下 那边我让她负责了
- I do. - She's working for me now. I've left her in charge.
有她一定能找得到
If anyone can find it, it's her.
我是戴安娜·斯坦顿 能给索普先生留言吗
Diana Stainton here. Can I leave a message for Mr Thorpe?
那个手提箱 我找到了
It's the suitcase. I found it.
-喂  -戴安娜 亲爱的 你已经穿着华丽睡衣了吗
- Hello? - Diana, darling. Are you in a gorgeous negligee?
没有 你呢
I'm not. Are you?
你就是那么幽默 听说你找到了那个破行李箱
Always so funny. They said you'd found that silly old suitcase.
在维多利亚行李寄存处 我明早去取
Waiting at Victoria left luggage. I'll collect it tomorrow morning.
具体在哪 我帮你取
Just give me the details, I'll do it for you.
不 巴塞尔先生让我找 就该我负责
No, Mr Bessell asked me to find it, so it's my responsibility.
手提箱属于都柏林的约瑟夫先生 我会还给他
The suitcase belongs to Mr Josiffe in Dublin, so I'll return it to him.
我来更方便
Much easier if I do it.
-我不同意 -拒绝绅士可不像你 戴安娜
- I disagree. - Not like you, Diana, saying no to a gentleman.
-晚安 索普先生  -我开车送你 说好了
- Goodnight, Mr Thorpe. - I'll drive you, that's what I'll do.
让你拎着那么重的手提箱可不行
Can't have you traipsing round town with a heavy suitcase, it's not right.
你还住在伊斯林顿吗
Are you still in that Islington lair?
-对  -明天早上八点整 我去接你
- Yes.  - Then I shall pick you up, eight o'clock sharp, tomorrow morning,
这就对了 拜拜
there's a good girl. Cheerio.
-谢谢...  -非常感谢
- Thank you... - Thank you very much.
非常抱歉 我得先回一下我的住处
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry, I just need to pop back to my flat.
我忘了点东西 上去一下就好
I remember I've left something at home. I won't be two ticks.
好吧
If you must.
马森宫廷酒店
-索普先生 你拿它干吗  -没什么
- Mr Thorpe! What do you need that for? - No matter!
索普先生 这不是你的
Mr Thorpe! That is not yours!
索普先生 你到底在干嘛 请你回答我
Mr Thorpe, what on earth are you doing?! I'd like an answer.
索普先生 你必须听我的
Mr Thorpe! I must insist!
索普先生 开门
Mr Thorpe, open this door!
那不是你的东西 索普先生 快开门让我进去
That is not your property. Mr Thorpe, let me in right now!
索普先生
Mr Thorpe!
索普先生 让我进去
Mr Thorpe, let me in!
索普先生
Mr Thorpe!
好了 麻烦你把东西
Now, then, if you would
交还约瑟夫先生 就大功告成了
very kindly return that to Mr Josiffe, I think we're done.
太好了 走吧
Splendid. Come along.
现在 我们可以放心地说
And that, I think we can safely say, is that.
永别了 诺玛·约瑟夫小姐
Farewell, Miss Norma Josiffe.
没错 不过你得答应我
Farewell indeed, but promise me,
帮帮忙 办好那张医保卡
sort out that insurance card, for God's sake.
好把他合法地跟我们联系起来吗
Give him something that connects us, officially?
想都别想
Absolutely not, no.
你爱过他吗
Did you love him?
老天
God.
抱歉 虽然过去了 但我很好奇
Sorry, old thing, but I have to wonder.
-爱过吗  -他是男的
- Did you? - Well, he was a man.
可你到底有没有爱过他
But did you love him at all?
哪怕一瞬间都没有吗
Not even once, for a moment?
佩德罗 不存在的
Pedro, that doesn't even exist.
对诺曼来说存在 他一下就爱上了你
It does for Norman. He seems to find it easy.
可不是吗
Doesn't he just?
我在想...
I wonder...
... 我是不是该嫉妒他
... should I envy him?
那天我跟利奥谈了谈
I spoke to Leo the other day.
利奥·艾比斯
Leo Abse,
-他还是很执着于同性恋合法化  -杰里米
- still obsessed with his bill to decriminalise homosexuality. - Jeremy.
-利奥  -就知道能碰到你
- Leo. - Thought I'd catch you.
什么事快说
You'll have to be very, very quick.
我正在准备 直捣黄龙
I'm going ahead with it, into the lions' den.
下个月有下议院普通议员议案
A Private Member's Bill for the Commons next month.
勇气可嘉
Well, you're a brave man.
我太太说我敢穿这件马甲就很勇敢
My wife says I'm brave for wearing this waistcoat.
别误会 我相信这些迷失的人也不开心
Make no mistake, though, I don't believe those lost souls will ever be happy,
但议会有义务帮助他们
but it's our duty in Parliament to help them.
可怜的同性恋
Poor bloody queers.
第一次提案 我问了大法官
My first proposal, I asked the Lord Chancellor.
你知道他说什么吗
Do you know what he said?
我不会参加任何
I will refuse to sit in any Cabinet meeting
讨论这种下流问题的内阁会议
where this filthy subject is even being discussed.
我们会批准同性恋俱乐部
We would be licensing buggers' clubs.
我不想花半点心思去翻查英国历史上
I have no desire t o go down in history as the man responsible
有哪些人致力于把鸡奸合法化
for legalising sodomy in Britain!
但最终 我找到一个帮肯我的人
But then, finally, I found someone to help me.
阿伦勋爵
Lord Arran.
-布菲吗  -布菲
- Boofy? - Boofy.
-阿伦勋爵  -叫我布菲就好
- Lord Arran. - Oh, call me Boofy.
-布菲  -这边走
- Boofy. - This way.
你穿多大的鞋
Now, what size are you?
42码 怎么了
A size eight, why?
-屋里有獾  -獾吗
- It's the badgers. - Badgers?
动物保护狂
Conservation mad.
我们在屋里放养獾
We've given them the run of the house.
这儿就有一只 这是罗茜
Oh, there's one! That one's Rosie.
厨房有个活板门 它们是从那儿钻进来的
Yes, there's a cat flap in the kitchen and in they come.
所以你得穿双靴子 保护脚踝
That's why you need the boots, to protect your ankles.
獾会咬人 让人患上肺结核
They bite, the little buggers. Give you tuberculosis.
-还有癣  -真是可怕的癣
- And ringworm. - Oh, terrible ringworm.
-菲奥娜 这是利奥  -利奥 这是菲奥娜
- Fiona, this is Leo. - Leo, this is Fiona.
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - How do you do?
我们正在庆祝
And we're celebrating.
她刚以时速131千米横渡温德米尔湖
She's just achieved speeds of 81.65 mph across Lake Windermere.
什么
I'm sorry?
原来阿伦勋爵夫人是个汽艇冠军
Turns out the Countess of Arran is a champion powerboat racer.
我的天
Good Lord.
该死的唐纳德·坎贝尔 我一定要赶上他
That bloody Donald Campbell, I'll catch him, the devil!
靴子 獾 等会儿我再让你看看沙袋鼠
Now, boots, badgers, and I must show you the wallabies later.
还有什么 对了 同性恋
What else? Oh, yes, queers.
十分感谢你的支持 布菲
But thank God for your support, Boofy.
我想不通
What puzzles me is that
异性恋总在锲而不舍地攻击
the heterosexual man is so relentless in his attack.
我们收到过恐吓信 恨意满满
We've had some dreadful letters, full of bile,
引用了申命记和利未记
quoting Deuteronomy and Leviticus.
但没人提到过登山宝训
No-one ever mentions the Sermon on the Mount.
还有人给我寄屎
I had shit sent to me.
一包屎 邮寄一包屎
A parcel of shit. Shit in the post!
人屎
Human shit!
我的秘书还以为那是肉酱
My secretary thought it was pate.
她说 "我把它扔了 阿伦勋爵 肉酱很快就坏了"
She said, "I threw it away, Lord Arran, it wouldn't keep."
你觉得我们有多大的把握
What chance do you think we stand?
我们的选票每天都在增加
Every day, we gain more votes.
但对有的人来说 还是太慢了
Not fast enough for some.
老天
Oh, goodness me.
-亲爱的...  -我没事
- Sweetheart... - I'm fine.
你可能会好奇 为什么我这把老骨头愿意帮忙
You might wonder why an old kidney like me would want to help.
我明白法律的力量
But I've seen what the law can do.
我弟弟...
My brother...
-... 伯爵七世  -彻头彻尾的同性恋
- ... the seventh Earl - Queer as springtime.
小时候在幼儿园 我伸出手...
When we were children, in the nursery, I'd reach out...
每晚都拉着他的手 直到他睡着 但是...
every night, held his hand until he slept, but...
他... 他那么聪明
he... he was such a clever boy.
你知道吗 他翻译了三剑客
He translated The Three Musketeers, did you know?
入选了企鹅经典
The Penguin Classic.
还有人不断死去 绞死 毒死 窒息
And the deaths go on, by hanging, by poison, by gas
有的人在恐惧和羞耻中自杀
men killing themselves through fear and shame.
但我不认为这是自杀
And I don't think it's suicide.
这是谋杀
I think it's murder.
他们是被大英帝国的法律谋杀的
They are murdered by the laws of the land.
是时候阻止这一切了
And I think it's time it stopped.
我们现在有能力去改变这条法律
Now we stand in a unique position to change the law
拯救他们的生命
and save their lives.
你支持我吗
Have I got your vote?
你是怎么回答的
And what did you say?
我同意了
Well, I said yes.
当然同意了
Of course I said yes.
老天 你把我当成什么人了
My God, what kind of man do you take me for?
想想 如果利奥·艾比斯赢了 就有了自由
It's astonishing to think, if Leo Abse wins, there will be freedom.
同性恋会收获同情 仅此而已
Those men will be free to be pitied, that's all.
我不在乎他们如何修改法律
I don't care what change they make to the law,
我的私事一旦被公开
if anything about me ever became public,
我向你保证 彼得
I give you my word, Peter,
我会朝着自己脑袋开一枪
I would put a gun to my head and blow my brains out.
那我会保护你 一如既往
Then, I shall protect you, as ever.
-谢谢你  -不客气
- Thank you. - Not at all.
明天见 别再胡思乱想了
Well, I shall see you tomorrow. Enough of this nonsense.
-还有正事要做 -未来还有很多挑战
- There's work to be done. - Exciting times ahead.
-非常 非常 非常多  -"非常 非常 非常"
- Very, very, very exciting, yes. - "Very, very, very."
-"非常 非常 非常..."  -行了 走吧
- "Very, very, very, very, very..." - Get out, come on.
大选 巴恩斯特普尔
索普·约翰·杰里米 自由党
Thorpe John Jeremy, Liberal Party.
16797票
16,797.
领袖选举
领袖选举结果如下
And the leadership election stands as follows.
胡森先生和卢伯克先生退出竞选
Mr Hooson and Mr Lubbock withdraw,
领袖选举
所以杰里米·索普当选为自由党领袖
so Mr Jeremy Thorpe is elected leader of the Liberal Party.
-杰里米  -非常感谢 谢谢
- Jeremy! - Thank you very much. Thank you.
佩德罗 胜者为王
Pedro. The best man won.
♪ 他真是个好伙计 他真是个好伙计 ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow, for he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ 他真是个好伙计 我们都是好伙计 ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow. And so say all of us. ♪
我用我祖父的剑发誓
I swear on my grandfather's sword
我会带领自由党一路前进
that I shall lead a Liberal crusade!
你是百年多来英国最年轻的党魁
You're the youngest man to lead a British political party in more than a century.
其实 小威廉·皮特更年轻
Well, Pitt the Younger was, well, younger.
他当选首相时才24岁
He was 24 when he became Prime Minister,
我已经落后了
so you could say I'm behind schedule.
-你有计划竞选首相吗  -你笑了...
- Is that the plan, Prime Minister?  - Well, you laugh...
佩德罗 我得出一个重要结论
Pedro, I've come to a very important conclusion.
如果我想在仕途上走得更远 最好得结婚
If I'm to get any further, I had better get married.
真的吗 你想娶谁 女王母亲吗
Really? Who do you have in mind, the Queen Mother?
我是认真的 我跟迈克·斯蒂尔谈过
I'm absolutely serious. I spoke to Mike Steele.
堪比斯芬克斯的迈克 我有个问题
The splendid and Sphinx-like Mike, a question -
如果我结婚 我们的选票会怎么样
how would it affect our ratings in the polls if I were to get married?
天 应该对你的选举有好处
Gosh, well, it might do you some good.
人们不会相信一个单身汉的
People don't trust a bachelor.
也许能上涨2%
We might go up by 2%.
真的吗 5%怎么样
Really? How about five?
好了就5% 愉快地决定了
Shall we say five? 5% it is.
有个明显的问题
There is one obvious problem.
我闭上眼睛 咬紧牙关
I'll close my eyes, grit my teeth
过几个月 我就说
and then after a few months, I'll say,
"亲爱的 我累了 老了 身体不行了"
"I'm tired and old and impotent, darling,"
-就这样混过去  -那个男的呢
- and that'll be that. - What about the men?
哪个男的
What men?
不管怎么说 不想听她抱怨
All the same, if she's not going to complain,
你就得找个没见过世面的女人
you'll need to find a girl who's led a sheltered life.
我会的
Then that is what I shall do.
我会让她成为世界上最幸福的女孩
I'll make her the luckiest girl in the world.
开始寻找吧
Let the hunt begin.
这件很棒 真的很棒
Oh, it's good. It's very good.
就是... 我跟你讲
It's... I'll tell you what it is,
这个内衬让它掉价了
it's the lining makes it look cheap.
要是换成深黄或朱红色
If that was in mustard or scarlet,
就会显得更精神
then I think that would really come alive.
天哪 你太有眼光了
Oh, my God. You've got quite an eye.
说真的 你可是那种
Mind you, you are one of those very lucky men
穿什么都帅的男人
you'd look good in anything.
我的天
Oh, my goodness!
继续 笑一笑
Go on, give us a smile.
戴上墨镜
Pop the glasses on.
再秀一下内衬
Flash us the lining again.
再骚气一点 很好
A bit more saucy. That's good.
你真的很适合当模特
You are very, very good at this.
明天十点
Now, Eve needs someone exactly your height,
伊芙就需要一个你这么高的模特
tomorrow at ten o'clock.
我真有这么棒吗
Am I really, though?
你为什么觉得我很棒 我不明白
Why am I good, do you think? I don't understand.
我做了什么就很棒
What am I doing that's good?
诺曼 很棒 往左边转
That's great, Norman. OK, I want you to turn to the left.
很好 保持那个姿势
Yeah, that's nice. Hold that.
太棒了 你天生适合吃这碗饭
Oh, gorgeous! You're a natural!
诺曼 很好
That's great, Norman.
东方承诺
用异国情调颠覆你的衣柜
不敢相信掀起了我引起了轰动
I can hardly believe all the fuss.
毕竟我只是个从贝克斯利黑斯来的男孩
I'm just a boy from Bexleyheath, after all.
帕特里克说他们很满意
Patrick said that they love it.
他们爱死你了
He said that they love you
希望你周四再去拍封面
and they want you back on Thursday for the cover!
我的天哪
Oh, my goodness!
多露点左半边  这样靠着
Show us more of your left side. Lean this way.
对 没错
Yeah, yeah.
就这样 很棒
Wow, that's great. Oh!
完美
Oh, nice, yes.
《荣誉》
追赶男性时尚潮流
24页全新样式
最新正装一览
最佳英式街拍
北德文郡
-我们都被蒙在鼓里  -我们
- We knew nothing about it. - Well, we
我们想秘密结婚 但是你们更狡猾
tried to keep the wedding day a secret, but you lot outfoxed us.
为了劝他去度蜜月 我简直费尽口舌
I had the devil's work, talking him into a honeymoon.
-杰里米总是很忙  -但现在不是了
- Jeremy is always so busy. - But not any more.
说实话 我们始于调情但终于爱情
I must say, what started as a dalliance has turned into something quite wonderful.
我是贝克斯利黑斯人
I may be from Bexleyheath
但我老妈在国外神秘地怀孕
but my mother became pregnant abroad, mysteriously,
所以谁都有可能是我老爸
so my father could be anyone.
诺曼 集中注意力
Just concentrate, Norman.
看着我 别玩球了
Look at me. Leave the ball, leave the ball where it is.
你玩得太开心了
You've been having too much fun.
看着我 对 好
Look at me. Yeah, OK.
专注
Concentrate.
-抱歉  -你能集中注意吗
- Sorry. - Just concentrate, yeah?
鲁伯特 哥们 看这里
Rupert, my friend, here, look.
看这里
And, look.
看 他换设备了
Oh, good, you see, he's changing the thingy.
我们速战速决 谢谢
As fast as we can now, thanks.
不想着凉
We don't want to get cold.
没事 我们非常开心 不是吗
No, it's fine, it's fine. We're perfectly happy. Isn't that right?
-小心  -我抱住他了 没事
- Careful. - I've got him, I've got him, I've got him.
-他有点困了  -小家伙 可不能睡着呀
- He's a bit sleepy. - Well, we can't have that, little chap,
大千世界等着你去探索呢
there's a whole world to see.
-你做得很好  -西莉亚说她等会儿过来
- Well done, you. - Celia said she'd pop in later.
想从我手上抢走他 可得费番功夫
She'll have a fight on her hands, taking him off me.
对吗 鲁伯特王子
Won't she, Prince Rupert?
你是小王子鲁伯特呢 还是小熊鲁伯特
Are you Prince Rupert or are you Rupert the Bear?
-你好 爸爸在叫你呢  -索普先生
- Hello. Daddy calling. Hello. - Mr Thorpe!
笑一个
And big smile.
就私下跟你说 我完全有可能
You know, it's entirely possible, between you and me,
是皇室成员
that I could be royalty.
诺曼 把墨镜摘掉
Norman! Right, you can take the glasses off.
-可我想戴着  -摘下来
- I'd like to keep them on, please. - Take them off.
拜托 来人给他眼眶上点遮瑕
Christ, can we get some make-up under his eyes, please?!
我准备道晚安了
Well, I'm going to say goodnight.
杰里米
Oh, Jeremy!
除非你先和我跳支舞
Not till you've danced with me.
-我拒绝  -我坚持
- I absolutely refuse. - But I insist.
-会吵醒孩子的  -他会为我们高兴的
- Well, that is going to wake the baby. - He'd be delighted for us.
好家伙 你会后悔的
Good Lord. You are making a grave error.
-是吗  -看吧
- Am I? - You see?
没那么难
It's not that hard.
就是这样
There we go.
抱歉 你看 我真的不会
Ooh! I'm sorry. You see, it was inevitable.
-我真...  -你故意的
- I'm so... - You did that on purpose.
-才不是  -就是
- Not at all, no. - You did.
我只会这么跳 那再试一次
That is me dancing. I'll try again.
别想就这样逃掉
Don't try and get out of this.
-我说了很抱歉  -你连续三次迟到了
- I said, I'm sorry! - You were late, three times in a row,
周二你连人影都没出现
and then on Tuesday, you didn't even turn up.
抱歉 诺曼 你不会再上杂志了
Sorry, Norman, you're off the books.
求你
Please.
开门 开门 我可以解释
Open the door, open the door, I can explain.
求你 求你了 林恩 别这样
Please, please, please! Please, Lyn, please! No!
林恩
Lyn!
考尔伯顿263号
Colberton 263.
我想找索普先生
Could I speak to Mr Thorpe, please?
抱歉 他现在不在 您是哪位
I'm sorry, he's not in at the moment. Who is this?
很抱歉打扰您
I'm sorry to bother you.
我在巴恩斯特布尔的自由俱乐部找到您电话的
I got your number from the Liberal Club in Barnstable.
-是索普夫人吗  -是的 您是哪位
- Is that Mrs Thorpe? - Yes, and who are you?
我是诺曼·约瑟夫
My name is Norman Josiffe.
他应该没提起过我
I don't suppose he mentioned me,
可我需要我的社保卡
but I need my National Insurance card.
能请您转告他吗
Can you tell him, please?
诺曼打来 需要他的社保卡
From me, from Norman, that I need it?
我在爱尔兰工作
I've been working in Ireland, you see,
现在出了点问题
and everything's gone a little bit wrong,
你们根本不知道社保卡有多重要
and I don't think you people know how it works.
它能决定我能不能领失业金
That card says whether I'm entitled to benefits,
我现在非常需要它
and I literally need it right now!
-我现在身无分文  -抱歉 我不明白
- I am penniless. - I'm sorry, I don't understand.
为什么你的社保卡在杰里米那里
Why would Jeremy have your card?
因为他曾经是我的雇主
Because he was my employer.
他是我的雇主 也是爱人
He was my employer and my lover.
他一次又一次地说他爱我 但我一无所有了
He told me he loved me again and again, and I've got nothing.
我只要拿到社保卡 就再也不纠缠你们了
All I need is that card and then I'll leave you alone.
你能转告他我改名字了吗
And can you tell him that I've changed my name?
他得把我现在的名字放在社保卡上
He will need to put that on the card.
我用的是艾尔登伯爵四世的姓
I've adopted the family name of the Fourth Earl of Eldon,
我应该是他的私生子
who sired me, I'm convinced, as his illegitimate son.
告诉杰里米我现在叫诺曼·斯科特
So tell Jeremy from now on my name is Norman Scott.
诺曼·斯科特
Norman Scott.
谢谢
Thank you.
斯科特
Scott.
诺曼·斯科特先生
Mr Norman Scott.
卡罗琳怎么说
And what did Caroline say?
太恶心了
It's disgusting.
他太恶心了
He was absolutely disgusting.
这么说吧 他在计划复仇
This man has been conducting, shall we say, a vendetta.
要是他有一点点让你觉得...
And if he was in any way trying to make you feel...
我不在乎 我不想再听到这件事了
I don't care. I don't want to hear anything about it.
他很明显是疯了
Well, he's obviously insane.
杰里米 再也不要提起这件事了
Jeremy, we will never discuss this in any way, ever.
明白了吗
Is that understood?
那我们现在怎么办
Then, what do we do?
-解决他  -怎么解决
- We get rid of him. - How?
恐吓他
We could scare him.
我朋友大卫 他认识些人
My friend David, he knows some men.
怎么 你是说要揍他吗
What? To rough him up, do you mean?
我觉得这没什么用
I'm not sure that would work.
诺曼这种感性的人 肯定会害怕的
Norman? He'd be terrified, the creature's pathetic.
我不确定 大家都容易犯这种错
I'm not sure. It's an easy mistake to make.
因为他有点娘 我们就觉得他软弱
He's effeminate and therefore we think he's weak,
可他整天在酒吧 俱乐部
but that man sits in pubs and clubs
别墅 旅馆向世界大声宣布
and houses and hotels telling all the world
他是同性恋
about his homosexuality out loud, all day long.
不论听众是谁 都影响不了他...
It doesn't bother him who's listening...
不管是牧师 主妇 老板 还是谁
priests or housewives or landlords or anyone.
他全然不在乎说出真相
He tells the truth and doesn't care.
没人会这么做 杰里米 我们更不会
No-one else does that, Jeremy. No-one. Certainly not us.
在英国 有且只有诺曼一个人
In this whole land, there is Norman and Norman alone.
这么坦率 我佩服他
To be blunt, he amazes me.
我觉得他是世上最强大的人之一
I think he's one of the strongest men in the world.
这样的话 我们就只有一个选择
Well, in that case, there is only one thing we can do.
杀了他
Kill him.
-你逗我呢...  -不 我是认真的
- Oh, if only we could...! - No, I mean it.
杀了他 拿伊做特
We kill him. Have him killed.
别胡说八道了
Don't be ridiculous.
他会毁了我 自由党 还有我的婚姻
He will destroy me and the party and my marriage.
要是他下次是跟记者说怎么办
What if the next person he talks to is a journalist, hm?
老天 杰里米 我们是议员
For God's sake, Jeremy, we're Members of Parliament.
我们不能在这里谈论谋杀
We can't sit here and discuss murder.
-比杀死病狗坏不了多少  -简直坏透了
- No worse than shooting a sick dog. - It's a damn sight worse.
我真的不在乎 不在乎是开枪打死他
I really don't care. I don't care if we shoot him
还是勒死他 毒死他
or we strangle him or we poison him
把他乱棍打死 还是装在袋子里扔进泰晤士河...
or we bludgeon him or we tie him up in a sack and drop in the Thames...
我们眼下只有一条活路...
there is only one way for us to survive...
诺曼·斯科特必须死 问题是 怎么做
Norman Scott has got to die. So, how?